

LUONG DUY DAT

4 10/11/2001

datld111001@gmail.com

Cau Giay District , Hanoi, Vietnam

+84-968-438299

About me

I am a student currently completing a Bachelor of Information Technology. My goal is to become an expert at Software Engineering and then establish my own company. I am intellectually curious, enjoy challenges and highly motivated to achieve my goal and make a positive contribution to society.

Education

University of Engineering and Technology, VNU

Information Technology

08/2019 - 06/2023

- GPA: 3.69/4.0
- Learn about the basic knowledge about Software Engineering, Information System, Computer Networks and Data Communication, and Computer science.
- Practice by doing some web, mobile application and AI project.

High School For Gifted Students, HNUE

Informatics Class

08/2016 - 06/2019

- Class: Specialized Informatics
- Learn algorithms for competitive programming.

Work Experiences

NMS Mobile Developer

02/2023 - present

 Responsible for working on two projects in the beginning month, supporting to design appealing user interfaces, implementing by Flutter Framework and interacting on a daily basis with graphic designers, back-end developers, and marketers.

MK Group Part-time Intern 12/2021 - 12/2022

- Learn how to program the mobile application using the Flutter framework with bloc pattern and practice in a Music

 Project
- Study penetration testing to check for exploitable vulnerabilities with Frida and some static toolkits.

Activities

Hanoi Association of Young Blood Donor Recruiters

Member

10/2019 - 10/2021

- Task: Mobilizing people to donate blood to save patient's lives
- Received a certificate of merit from association president for my outstanding achievements in the blood donation movement

Prizes and Awards

Viet Nam National Informatics Contest for High School Seniors

2017-2018

Skills

Flutter Firebase

Github and Docker HTML5 & CSS

Reactjs Object-Oriented Programming

Certificates

(10/2022)

7.0

Projects

Specialized Internships and Training Programs Management System - Dissertation 12/2022 - present

Description: Mobile App for the student to understand more profound about their chosen training programs and assist them in planning a learning process for the future. This app also improve the school's management of students' internships and help university choose a more suitable curriculum.

Technique: Flutter, Laravel, Microservice

- Indentify business domain.
- Designing and deciding on the visual layout of a mobile app.
- Designing backend and databases.
- Create responsive user interface

STOCK PREDICTION APP - Self project

09/2022 - 12/2022

Description: Mobile App help people follow and predict the stock price. In addition, app is a place liked a group for each stock symbol for people to discuss and gain knowledge about this symbol.

Technique: Flutter, Firebase, Keras

- Design the front-end UI by Flutter Framework.
- Using Firebase to store data.
- Build LSTM model to predict stocks price by Keras API.
- Get Stocks price from Yahoo Finance API.